The past never forgets.
The Girl in the Spider's Web is a action, crime,
thriller film directed by Fede Álvarez.
After being enlisted to recover a dangerous computer program, hacker Lisbeth Salander and journalist Mikael
Blomkvist find themselves caught in a web of spies, cybercriminals and corrupt government officials.
Lisbeth Salander, played by Claire Foy.
Mikael Blomkvist, played by Sverrir Gudnason.
Edwin Needham, played by LaKeith Stanfield.
Camilla Salander, played by Sylvia Hoeks.
Frans Balder, played by Stephen Merchant.
August Balder, played by Christopher Convery.
The Girl in the Spider's Web is a 2018 action thriller film directed by Fede Álvarez, who co-wrote the screenplay with Jay Basu and Steven Knight, based on the
2015 novel of the same name by David Lagercrantz, which in turn was based on characters introduced in the Millennium book series by Stieg Larsson.
The film acts as a soft reboot and sequel to The
Girl with the Dragon Tattoo (2011).
It stars Claire Foy in the role of Lisbeth Salander, and follows Salander as she battles
against a mysterious notorious organization, the Spiders, who seek world dominance.
Sverrir Gudnason, Lakeith Stanfield, Sylvia Hoeks, and
Stephen Merchant appear in supporting roles.
The Girl in the Spider's Web had its premiere at the Rome Film Festival on October 24, 2018, and was released
in Sweden on October 26, and in the United States on November 9, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
A box-office disappointment, the film grossed only $35.2 million worldwide against a production budget of $43
million and received generally mixed reviews from critics, although Foy's performance was praised.
The film explores themes of hacker, based on novel or
book, sweden, stockholm, sweden, sequel.
The tone is intense.